(Sheldon:)Would you like to play
a physics car game I invented
called "I Can't Spy"?
(Sheldon:)It's all the nail-biting
tension of "I Spy"
(Sheldon:)but the added fun of subatomic
particles and waves
(Sheldon:)outside the visible
spectrum.
(Leonard:)If it's half as much fun as
"One Times Ten to the Fourth
Bottles of Beer on the Wall,"
(Leonard:)I'm in.
(Sheldon:)I'll begin.
(Sheldon:)Uh, I can't spy
with my little eye...
(Sheldon:)...something passing
right through us.
(Leonard:)That soy Frappuccino I had.
(chuckles)
(Sheldon:)Will you please
play the game?
(Sheldon:)I can't spy
with my little eye
(Sheldon:)something passing
right through us.
(Leonard:)I don't know, um...
(Leonard:)If 65 billion
solar neutrinos pass
through a square centimeter
every second,
(Leonard:)given the surface
area of this car is
(Leonard:)about 60,000
square centimeters,
(Leonard:)that means 3.9 times ten
to the 15th solar neutrinos?